(Howard:)where all the black-market
weapon trades go down.
(Raj:)I don't think my character
should be in a place like this.
(Raj:)Everyone's undressing
her with their eyes.
(Howard:)Maybe if you stop
dropping your sword
(Howard:)and bending over to pick it up.
(Leonard:)Okay, what exactly
are we looking for?
(Howard:)Redheaded troll,
goes by the name of Glumly.
(Howard:)According to the
message boards,
(Howard:)if you want to
move stolen goods
(Howard:)and it's after school
hours, he's your guy.
PRIYA: Leonard,
is this going
(Priya:)to take much longer?
I thought we were
(Priya:)going to spend
some time together.
(Leonard:)Uh, we are.
In the meantime,
(Leonard:)you're welcome to whip up
a quick character and join us.
(chuckles):
Seriously?
(Leonard:)Well, you have to put
in a credit card number,
(Leonard:)but it's fun.
(Priya:)Maybe I should just go home.
(Howard:)Our troll just walked
in! I got him!
(Leonard:)We got him.
We're almost done.
WOLOWITZ:
So, how do
(Howard:)you guys want
to play this?
(Sheldon:)Be ruthless.
You tell him
(Sheldon:)if he doesn't start talking,
we'll register a complaint
(Sheldon:)with his Internet
service provider.
Sheldon, what if he gets his
Internet from his cable company?
(Raj:)He could lose his HBO and all their
delightful original programming.